PATRICK CAMILLO

Information Security Analyst



+55 11 971148588



patrick.camillo@outlook.com

ABOUT ME

Experienced in managing IT infrastructure for multiple customers, providing service and support to users, and implementing new technologies in environments. Advanced knowledge of Linux. Contact with software development in JavaScript and RPAs in Python. Experienced in PowerShell and Microsoft environments, including Office 365, Azure and AWS. Native Brazilian Portugues. Intermediate knowledge of the Salesforce ecosystem. Passionate about improving processes and automating tasks.

EDUCATION

2019 - 2024 | FACULDADES METROPOLITANAS UNIDAS | BRAZIL

Computer Science

EXPERIENCE

2022 - CURRENT | 9NET TECNOLOGIA

Information Security Analyst

Management of network monitoring and reporting tools (PRTG, Zabbix, and Grafana). Management and maintenance of SASE environments (Netskope), CDN and WAF (Akamai) tools. Working on projects to improve the environment by implementing new technologies. Maintenance of infrastructure, networks, servers and equipment.

2018 - 2022 | TFA TECNOLOGIA

Support Analyst

IT environment management for multiple customers. Working on projects to improve the environment by implementing new technologies. Development of RPAs in Python for web automation. Deploying and managing applications hosted with Docker on Linux servers. Dealing with technology suppliers. Technical support for users. Infrastructure, server and equipment maintenance.

OTHER COURSES

CCNAV7: INTRODUCTION TO NETWORKS

2024 | Cisco Networking Academy

ADVANCED LINUX

2023 | Udemy - Matheus Müller

COMPUTER NETWORK INSTALLATION AND REPAIR

2018 | Senac SP